http://rangeairevision.com/legal/

Jane Harvey
Cart (0)
Rangeaire Vision
About
Legal
Website Terms and Conditions
By using this website ("RangeaireVision") or any of its contents, you agree to comply with these terms and conditions. From time to time RangeaireVision (ABN 30 285 366 998) may change these terms and conditions at its discretion and without notice, and by continuing your use you accept the revised terms and conditions.
Website not advice
This website provides general information, not advice. The use of this website (including sending any communication to RangeaireVision through it) or any of its contents does not create any obligation of RangeaireVision to provide advice to you, and you must not rely upon any of the contents without obtaining corresponding advice from RangeaireVision.
Disclaimer
The information in this website is of a summary nature, might not address issues applicable to you, or might make assumptions that do not apply to you. Parts of this website may not be updated regularly, or at all, so that they may be out of date.
To the extent permitted by law, RangeaireVision makes no warranty or representation about the accuracy, completeness or fitness for any purpose of the contents of this website, or that this website is free of viruses or other code that is harmful or may assist in causing harm.
To the extent permitted by law, any condition or warranty regarding this website or its contents that would otherwise be implied (by statute or otherwise) into these terms and conditions is excluded.
Links to other websites
This website may contain links to other websites for your convenience. We do not control the content of those websites or endorse it in any way. To the extent permitted by law, we make no warranties or representations regarding that content and exclude any liability to you in relation to it.
Restrictions on use
You must only use this website for lawful purposes. You must also take your own precautions to ensure that your access to this website does not expose you to viruses or other code that is harmful or may assist in causing harm.
Copyright notice
Copyright in this website is owned by Jane and Bob Harvey ("Proprietors"). Subject to any exceptions that cannot be excluded under any applicable law, and subject to the rights granted to you in this copyright notice, the Proprietors reserve all rights in this website and you must not in any way reproduce, publish, communicate or adapt any part of this website without the prior written approval of the Proprietors.
You may, for non-commercial purposes:
Browse or print a copy of any part of this website solely in order to view it; and
Communicate any part of this website to others provided that the relevant part is a self-contained whole (e.g. an entire article), you include an attribution to RangeaireVision and you include these terms and conditions.
Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy is simple. This website does not collect and maintain any personal information. Nor does it disclose any personal information to third parties.
When you only browse the website, we do not collect your personal information. We do not use cookies nor any third party trackers such as Google Analytics. For statistical purposes, our service provider may log anonymous information such as time of visit and which pages have been viewed. These logs are temporary and are fully secured.
If you provide information using our Contact Us form, then the supplied name and email will only be used for replying to that inquiry. If a third party provides us with information, for example PayPal for the purpose of a purchase, then the supplied information will only be used in relation to supplying that purchase. We don't have access to any credit card numbers - that information is only collected and used by the bank and payment provider.
You can obtain further information in relation to this privacy policy, ask questions about it or provide any comments, then please Contact Us.
DMCA (USA only)
Rangeaire Vision has compliance procedures to deal with Digital Millennium Copyright Act. Rangeaire Vision has tried to ensure that all material is original, or is referenced or has the permission of the owner. If you find your copyrighted material on this site and don't want them there, please let us know by sending us a copyright infringement notification using the contact details on our Contact Us page. The infringement notice must be in writing and contain the following:
Your name, address, telephone number, and email address so that Rangeaire Vision can contact you.
Sufficient detail identifying the copyrighted work that you believe has been infringed upon including the URL on this website that shows the work.
Sufficient detail identifying the material that you claim is infringing the copyrighted work listed in item 2. You must include URLs for the material you want taken down.
The statement: "I have a good faith belief that use of the copyrighted materials described above is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law."
The statement: "I swear, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate and that I am the copyright owner or am authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner."
Your signature.
Please also note that under the US Copyright Act, any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.
Liability
To the extent permitted by law, RangeaireVision excludes all liability to you on any basis (including negligence) for any loss or damage, however caused, which you may suffer in relation to your use of this website or any contents.
To the extent permitted by law, any liability of RangeaireVision in connection with this website under any statutory right (including any condition or warranty implied by law or any guarantee or other right under any statute) that by law cannot be excluded is limited at the option of RangeaireVision to the resupply of the relevant services or the payment of the cost of same.
General
If any part of any of these terms and conditions is void, then the part that is void may be severed. Where used in these terms and conditions, the phrase "including" must be read as "including, but not limited to" and references to the content of this website include any content submitted by a third party. Other than any local laws applicable to you that by law cannot be excluded, these terms and conditions are governed by the laws of Victoria, Australia.
On this page
Legal
Website not advice
Disclaimer
Links to other websites
Restrictions on use
Copyright notice
Privacy Policy
DMCA (USA only)
